{
  "title": "Capitales de España",
  "bg_color1": "lightgray",
  "bg_color2": "lightblue",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "Andalucía",
      "answer": "Sevilla"
    },
    {
      "question": "Aragón",
      "answer": "Zaragoza"
    },
    {
      "question": "Asturias",
      "answer": "Oviedo"
    },
    {
      "question": "Baleares",
      "answer": "Palma de Mallorca"
    },
    {
      "question": "Canarias",
      "answer": "Santa Cruz de Tenerife y Las Palmas de Gran Canaria"
    },
    {
      "question": "Cantabria",
      "answer": "Santander"
    },
    {
      "question": "Castilla-La Mancha",
      "answer": "Toledo"
    },
    {
      "question": "Castilla y León",
      "answer": "Valladolid"
    },
    {
      "question": "Cataluña",
      "answer": "Barcelona"
    },
    {
      "question": "Extremadura",
      "answer": "Mérida"
    },
    {
      "question": "Galicia",
      "answer": "Santiago de Compostela"
    },
    {
      "question": "La Rioja",
      "answer": "Logroño"
    },
    {
      "question": "Madrid",
      "answer": "Madrid"
    },
    {
      "question": "Murcia",
      "answer": "Murcia"
    },
    {
      "question": "Navarra",
      "answer": "Pamplona"
    },
    {
      "question": "País Vasco",
      "answer": "Vitoria-Gasteiz"
    },
    {
      "question": "Valencia",
      "answer": "Valencia"
    }
  ]
}
